webhire.com 2005-12-30

# Webhire | Privacy | Attract, Retain, Achieve

Webhire, Inc. – Privacy Policy

Webhire, Inc. (“Webhire”) is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and business partners.This Privacy Policy explains the information gathering and dissemination practices used at our [www.webhire.com](http://www.webhire.com/) website.

When you access the public areas of our website, we do not require that you disclose personally identifiable information.  Our web servers log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to help us determine if there are problems with our website, to gather usage statistics, and to administer and improve our website.  We do not link your IP address to any personal information unless you have logged into our website through registration and a password.

In order to access certain parts of our website, we may ask you to register with us.  During the registration process we collect personally identifiable information or information about your organization, such as contact information (like name, address, email address, etc.).  Additionally, we may collect personally identifiable information when you register to attend a seminar or webinar, ask to be included in an email or other mailing list, or submit your information for any other reason.  We use customer contact information to send information about our company, product information, newsletters, and promotional material from some of our business partners.  We do not sell or rent personally identifiable information to other organizations.  On occasion, we may share personally identifiable information with our business partners.

We do not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us. You may “opt out”, or remove your name from our database, change your information, or request that your information not be used for direct marketing purposes at any time, by contacting us at [remove@webhire.com](mailto:remove@webhire.com).

As is the case with many websites, when you visit our site or complete a registration form, we will place a “cookie” on your computer.  A cookie is a small, encrypted data string our server writes to your hard drive that contains your unique user ID that helps us identify you more quickly when you return.  A cookie cannot be used to access or otherwise compromise data on your computer, and we do not use cookies to follow your click stream on the Internet generally, but may use them to determine which pages or information you find most useful or interesting on our own website.  You can choose to change your browser settings to disable cookies if you do not want us to establish and maintain a unique user ID.  Please be aware that cookies might be required to complete certain functions on our website.

Our website may contain links to other websites.  Please be aware that our Privacy Policy does not apply to these other websites and we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices employed by these websites.

As our business and technology changes, we may occasionally update this Privacy Policy.  Notice of any revisions will be posted to this Privacy Policy web page.

If you have comments or questions about our Privacy Policy, please send them to us at [info@webhire.com](mailto:info@webhire.com).
